earningstation.com 2017-05-21

# EarningStation – Free Gift Cards for Surveys and Videos

**1\. Information Collected**

All Users must provide the following information in order to join EarningStation.com: 

  * Name 
  * Phone Number 
  * Email Address 
  * Password 

Users may be required to provide subsequent demographic information in order to receive Signup Bonus(es) and/or qualify for other promotions. Demographic information includes, but is not limited to: 

  * birth date 
  * gender 
  * marital status 
  * education completed 
  * household income 
  * and number of children in household 

We may also ask you to provide on an optional and voluntary basis information regarding health and wellness issues relevant to you or your family. 

**2\. Means of Collection**

Users may join EarningStation.com by completing one of our signup forms, through Co- Registration, or other means as we may determine at any time in the future. in short:   
You must provide basic demographic information to use EarningStation.com. Additional demographic data may be collected in order to improve your experience with the program. 

**I. USE OF INFORMATION**

User information is used by EarningStation.com in all of the following ways:   
a. E-Mail Address is used to send paid email advertisements and important announcements about EarningStation.com to User   
b. Mailing Address is used to send payments earned by User or otherwise communicate with User   
c. Demographic information is used to target advertisements to User   
d. Username, E-Mail Address, and Password are used for User protection to restrict access to their account   
e. User information may be sold or disclosed to third parties as described in Sections II.2 and III below   
f. Cookies or similar tracking technology may be used as described in Section IV below   
g. Information may be used in additional ways as posted on this Privacy Policy in the future. 

2\. Sharing of Information 

EarningStation.com does not rent, sell, or share User information, except in the following circumstances: 

a. We are required to release User information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes   
b. Part or all of our business is sold to, merged with, or acquired by another company, in which case some or all User information would then belong to said company   
c. We share User information when co-registration boxes (explained below) are checked during the course of registration   
d. We suspect a User of committing fraud, in which case User information may be shared during the course of our investigation   
e. We may sell or share User information to other advertisers or businesses whom we believe you may find useful and in order to enhance the service provided to our Users   
f. We may share User information with third parties as reasonably necessary for us to operate this website and to provide offers and services to Users   
g. California Residents Only: If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive: 

(i) information identifying any third party company(ies) to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information pertaining to you for the company’s direct marketing purposes; and   
(ii) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. To obtain such information you must make a request in writing to Customer Service using the contact information provided Section V of this Privacy Policy. 

In short:   
We will use your email address to send you email communications, your home address to mail your check, and other collected demographic information to personalize our emails and web site for you. In short:   
EarningStation.com will only share your information in the cases listed here. 

**II. CO-REGISTRATION**

1\. Definition   
EarningStation.com signup pages may contain co-registration checkboxes, where Users can choose to “co-register” for other Web Sites during their registration with EarningStation.com by checking the checkbox next to the co-registration Offer. Users are not required to select any co-registration boxes to join EarningStation.com;however, they may be required to do so in order to qualify for Signup Bonus(es) and/or other promotions. 

2\. Information Sharing   
When a User co-registers for an Offer by checking the co-registration checkbox, any information they provide to EarningStation.com may be shared with the Advertiser associated with the co-registration Offer. EarningStation.com cannot control what Advertisers subsequently do with that information. 

3\. Privacy on Other Sites   
This website may contain links to third party websites. We provide these links for your convenience, We do not review, control or monitor the privacy practices of websites operated by others. We are not responsible for the performance of these sites or for your business dealings with them. Your use of other websites is subject to the terms and conditions of those websites, including the privacy policies of those websites. 

In short:   
Our Advertisers each have their own Privacy Policies. 

**III. COOKIES AND THIRD PARTY TRACKING TECHNOLOGY**

A “cookie” is a small data file that may be saved to and stored on your computer when you visit a website or open an email. Cookies permit a website to “remember” whether your computer has visited the website before and helps the website create a more personalized experience for you and records activities taken by you, such as offers completed. In addition to cookie technology, EarningStation.com and our Advertisers use additional third party technology and tracking tools to record offers and activities completed by you, friends referred by you, and to communicate information about you, such as demographic information (e.g., age, gender), in order to target offers and advertisements to specific groups as requested by Advertisers. Cookies and other tracking technology is collectively referred to as “Cookies and Recording Tools.” 

1\. About Cookies and Third Party Technology. 

Your computer permits you to change the settings on your web browser to not accept and/or disable Cookies and Recording Tools. However, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools used by EarningStation.com and our Advertisers, you may not be able to use certain functions on certain websites. More importantly, if you do not accept Cookies and Recording Tools you will not receive credit for offers or other actions completed by you because we and our Advertisers are unable to track and record your activity. If you do not want to accept Cookies and Recording Tools, you must stop using this website. 

2\. Third Party Cookies 

Notwithstanding anything else in this policy, we or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, that we may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to http://www.aboutads.info/choices. 

3\. Referral and Affiliate Tracking 

EarningStation.com uses cookies in order to track new User registrations. This ensures Users are properly credited for referring other Users, as well as to track earnings for our Affiliates. 

After a User has logged into the EarningStation.com Member’s Section, cookies are used to remember their Username and Password so they do not need to be entered during every visit to our Web Site. Users can logout of the Member’s Section if they do not wish to have this information saved. 

**IV. CONTACT US**

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, desire not to receive information about products or services we think may be of interest to you, or with to access, delete your information, wish to request information pursuant to Section II.2.(f) of this Privacy Policy, please email us at support@earningstation.com or send us a letter by first class postage prepaid U.S. mail or overnight courier to the following address: 

Customer Service   
EarningStation.com   
400 Trade Center, Suite 4960   
Woburn, MA 01801
